(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR
VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
I'm glad the sport-gasm festival
ended without any incidents.
Though it would have been perfect if
I could have found my destiny XXX.
Now I can resume the order
from the SHO.
The search for Fumino Kotoyose, right?
Touka-chan, any leads?
The place where the target
is likely to appear next...
is...
The Pervert Land.
MINOTSUKI ACADEMY
Get pregnant now!
My womb... isn't falling much.
I don't know... what to say.
This is...
TOSHIAKI HITOURA
ADVOCATE FOR FREE LEWDNESS
The assassination of that man.
I don't know the circumstances...
but I can't just leave Fumino-chan alone.
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
What's the situation
with Fumino Kotoyose?
FS is currently searching for her.
But the information
is quite limited.
Watch your tone, Reizeiin.
Do you think SHO is paying
for your scholarships as a charity?
We exist to enforce
the Perverted Ordinance on the islanders...
and eventually spread it nationwide.
Therefore, any obstacle must be eliminated.
Am I wrong?
You are absolutely right.
That's enough.
Roger.
Ensure the security
for the speech is thorough.
Do not disappoint Hitoura-sama.
Touka-sama, are you ok?
No worries.
So annoying. Should I kill them?
It's fine, Ikuko.
Touka-sama.
Here's the security deployment data.
If there are no issues,
I'll share it with SHO.
That won't be necessary.
Huh?
Why is that?
Hmm...
In some way...
Alright, this should do it.
Asa-chan, looks like you're doing well.
At this rate, we should find
information on Fumino Kotoyose soon...
I'm playing a game right now.
It's called "Instanto Denudo."
A game where we strip each other...
with magic to uncover
the secrets of crotch magic.
Alright, enough with the game.
It's time for a strategy meeting.
Let's organize the new information...
we got from the backdoor
I installed on FS's PC.
To summarize,
the target wears a kimono,
has a distinctive hair color,
and is skilled at long-range sniping.
Also, for some reason, she seems
to be targeting Governor Hitoura.
The person who created the ordinance?
I don't know why,
but if FS has gathered this much information...
They must be targeting Fumino Kotoyose.
Everyone.
Something arrived.
Heave-ho.
This is...
This must be from our patron,
the mysterious person.
What is it?
It's a recently developed substance
called D10-O.
Normally it's soft like so,
but when it receives a strong impact,
the molecules bond together and it hardens.
It got on my face.
Giving a facial to a loli is sinful.
I'm not a loli, though.
Bonding together and getting hard...
Are you thinking of something lewd?
Yeah, exactly.
Ahh, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Hmm...
Ah, welcum!
This place is...
an adult shop?
Uwah!
Just as I expected.
From classics to new releases,
they have every kind of onahole imaginable.
Look, Nanase.
This one can automatically warm itself
to body temperature.
Drastically reduces
the cold sensation upon insertion.
Washing it afterward
would feel even more empty.
Life is empty anyway, right!?
Onii-san.
You have great taste, and great assets.
I highly recommend that product.
Huh? You look like the Legendary XXX.
Nah, that can't be it.
How about this new model vibrator?
I guarantee it will enhance
a couple's passionate night.
A couple?
Here, here.
Please lightly give it a try.
Wow, it looks great "in" you, ma'am.
Huh?
With its chic color, you can even
use it for ceremonial occasions.
Ceremonial occasions?
Alright, I'll take this one.
Jun?
Thanks for cumming!
How will you be paying?
With PyPy.
A FLEETING HYMEN
WIFE - VIBRATOR - LOTION
Combining this vibrator...
with the new material we received
from the mysterious person,
we can make a powerful weapon.
A weapon?
Ah, s-so that's what it is.
It's so embarrassed that I'm sweating.
So hot.
Isn't it bad for the model XXX...
to get flustered by a mere vibrator?
That's right.
That's the character I'm playing.
Nanase, you're surprisingly
bad at pretending.
Look who's talking, virgin.
Watch this.
Beep beep.
Backing up, backing up.
I'll park in that tight garage XXX.
Get pregnant now!
Even though you have
an automatic-only dick.
You're in the way. Move.
What?
You want me to park
in your garage too?
Unfortunately, it's full.
Beep beep, XXX up, XXX up.
That's not a garage, it's a parking area.
For an automatic,
don't you dare stall on me.
Yahoo!
See?
As expected.
Inside the condom
is just a cornstarch slurry, though.
Well, this is my weapon.
My hair is also extensions.
Is that so?
I'm also wearing contacts.
That's how I've managed...
to look flashy like a XXX
as much as possible.
But when you're around,
that side of me just comes out.
Nanase...
Hey, shouldn't we give a name...
to our team?
Eh?
Ah, you're right.
Actually, I've already thought of one.
DICKPOSIUM AT PERVERT LAND
ON MAY 12TH (SATURDAY) AT 13:00
What's this?
XXXposium?
That's quite interesting.
No, that's not it.
Huh?
"She seems to be
targeting Governor Hitoura."
The speech is tomorrow.
Are you really going?
I'm not the type of woman
that would abandon you.
I can at least be your shield.
I'm a big girl after all.
Let's do our best.
DICKPOSIUM AT PERVERT LAND
ON MAY 12TH (SATURDAY) AT 13:00
To commemorate the XXX,
anyone who wants to shake hands
with Hamedori-kun, please line up.
A handshake isn't enough.
I want a handjob.
Handshake, handjob, sex-shake.
Hame?
Get pregnant now!
Please bang in order.
REPRODUCE JAPAN
Despite the unprecedented recession
our country is facing,
Seiran Island has continued
to achieve economic growth.
Even so, the demand
for lewdness is gradually increasing.
In the cumming years,
Japan will become a Perverted Nation,
and its name will be known
throughout the world.
That said...
Oh my.
A suspicious dick
is approaching from point C3.
Delta 1, confirm the womb.
Delta 1, target's location confirmed.
That is...
I've got you, target.
Squad 2, begin suppression!
The more you pull the trigger,
the happier you get.
Fire, fire, fire, fire—!
What's going on here?
So she's appeared,
just as Touka-sama predicted.
Mozume.
They're heading this way
as if to taunt us.
I've already locked on.
I'll send you back to your mother's womb.
Oh?
Is this... jamming?
What is it this time?
Who's interrupting my happy time?
Jamming and a smokescreen, have they come?
The Anti-Copulation Force.
As expected,
she's targeting Governor Hitoura.
That Fumino Kotoyose.
That's fine,
but what are we supposed to do?
Fire at will.
The enemy already predicted our moves.
Disperse and create a diversion.
- Got it!
- Roger!
Switching radar to Dogfight Mode.
Master Arm on.
Let's go! Engage!
Fumino Kotoyose is receiving support
from the Anti-Copulation Force.
All units, suppress them as planned.
Roger.
Keep the smokescreen up.
Now's our chance
to secure Fumino Kotoyose...
Found you.
It's been a while since we met
on the mountain, Anti-Copulation Force.
How did you know my position?
You may be able to fool the GPS,
but you can't hide
the stench of semen that clings to a man.
What a dog-like imitation.
Now, with honor, let out your precum.
Vibrator?
This one's special-made.
Normally it's soft and pliable,
but when impacted, the molecules
of the new material bond and harden.
You mere sex toy!
Its steel-like hardness is like...
the dick of a young man
with pent-up libido.
It can pierce any enemy.
Penetrate!
Its name is truly the Penetrator!
My precum...
I've made you pay back
the debt from before.
Nukitashi.
Fumino Kotoyose is...
Cum here, Anti-Copulation Force.
Hey, isn't that Nanase Katagiri?
The Legendary XXX?
How could that be!
Fire!
That was a close call.
A... an umbrella?
Such hardness!
Where did you buy it?
Unfortunately, it's not for sale.
It's a Vibrator-Bat Umbrella.
There is no time to be scared, Rin-san!
As if I'm scared.
Turn into ashes!
Ah, um...
Go.
The little girl
will guide you to a safe place.
Little girl?
Found her.
Target has stopped.
1 o'clock, distance 391.
It's me!
What is it?
We're being targeted.
Is it the enemy?
They're gone.
You're Fumino-chan, right?
Now, come with big sister.
Ah, who are you guys?
Anti-Copulation Force.
We're here to help Fumino-chan.
Help her? How?
How about that?
- Hmm?
- Heh?
A truck?
Can you drive?
I'll manage somehow with spirit.
Eh?
Ah, this car's handbrake is an anal pearl.
Let's depart!
Spirit, Energy, Misaki!
The object is moving towards
the square in a truck.
They have a skilled driver
as an accomplice.
Got it, we'll follow immediately.
Heh... You can dodge that?
She is even faster
than the radar's detection.
Nice to meet you.
The cutest
and strongest captain of FS Squad 1,
it's me, Ikuko Onabuta-chan.
This aura...
She's clearly on a different level
from the other FS members.
Anti-Copulation Force, was it?
I heard you're talking about
bringing down the hammer on loveless sex.
The pleasure of simply
indulging in carnal desires,
shall I teach you about it?
Don't underestimate me.
I will never engage in lewd sex.
Absolutely not.
When you resist,
it just turns me on even more.
You sure talk a lot!
Good reaction, but...
Damn it...
I'm better at ground techniques, you know?
Continue moving forward!
The target is just a little further.
In other words, the Perverted Ordinance...
Good.
She is here, Touka-sama.
is an unprecedented sexual policy.
It's already garnering attention
from local governments across the country.
This is Null Base.
Where's Wata-chan?
My brother's been taken out.
Eh?
We have to help him quickly.
What do we do, Fumino-chan?
This is...
A happier, freer,
and more liberated life...
has a significant relationship
with daily health.
Everyone should be
experiencing this firsthand.
Fumino-chan.
We're turning back.
Thank you very much
for your attention.
Now, to conclude,
please join me in saying...
"Let's spread the...
the circle of lewd sex!"
It seems there was
some commotion.
That was...
Is it Fumino?
Well, I wonder.
How dare you
speak to Hitoura-sama like that!
Submit a report on the commotion
by the end of today.
What a shame.
My strength...
Let see...
what kind of XXX XXX do you have?
Stop it!
You mean, "Fuck me," right?
Hey, it's not hard.
Hah, too bad.
I'm impotent.
I can't have sex.
It'll get hard.
If I'm your partner,
no matter what kind of XXX,
it will get rock hard.
T-This voice...
Come on, feel it.
My cute voice tickling your ears.
My head is spinning.
The sweet scent tickling your nose.
The soft breasts pressed against you.
Don't tell me it's aphrodisiac effect?
Get bigger.
Alright, erection complete.
Impossible.
Eh, why were you hiding it?
Such a cool dick.
Is there such a thing as
a lame dick?
Oh, scary.
I don't know why you're angry,
but let's get started.
S-Stop, wait.
I won't wait.
Uwaaah!
Alright, congratulations
on losing your virginity.
Ah, what is this?
It's in, it's inside!
Ah, not only is it big,
but the shape is perfect too.
I'm being completely violated.
So you were hiding this.
I might have found something amazing.
It's over.
It's already over.
Ah, so good.
Amazing.
I lost my virginity.
Junnosuke Tachibana has just died.
Then I...
will have to live on while my pride...
and my self-respect
is continuously taken from me?
But when you're around,
that side of me just comes out.
No way!
Ah, it twitched and jumped.
The dick got bigger.
Still getting bigger...
Wait, it's still getting bigger?
It's not just mine.
It's still getting bigger?
No way. This is physically impossible!!
Aaaaaah!
I'm not alone.
No way! What is this? It's so hard...
I'm cumming!
I'll never let anyone take it from me.
I've finally found it, my destiny XXX!
D-Did we just hit something?
I-I hope it's just my imagination.
Lord have mercy.
Jun, are you okay?
Yeah, somehow.
Ouch!
W-Who are you people?
We have no obligation
to introduce ourselves,
but I'll make an exception
so listen up.
We are the ones who bring down the hammer
on all loveless, perverted sex.
The Anti-Copulation Faction.
Eh?
The NLNS.
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder, have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me